{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259645802","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259645802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" cce51a89-ef88-460c-b44c-a49ba0d381fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_3-2-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259651030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259651030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" cce51a89-ef88-460c-b44c-a49ba0d381fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_8-1-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259657726","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259657725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" cce51a89-ef88-460c-b44c-a49ba0d381fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-5-8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259663650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259663650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" cce51a89-ef88-460c-b44c-a49ba0d381fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_9-7-3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259668421","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259668421"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" cce51a89-ef88-460c-b44c-a49ba0d381fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_8-4-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259673274","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259673274"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" cce51a89-ef88-460c-b44c-a49ba0d381fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-5-0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259678121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259678120"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" cce51a89-ef88-460c-b44c-a49ba0d381fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_7-6-1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259684766","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259684765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" cce51a89-ef88-460c-b44c-a49ba0d381fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-4-1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259689903","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259689903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" cce51a89-ef88-460c-b44c-a49ba0d381fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_4-8-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259696420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259696420"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" cce51a89-ef88-460c-b44c-a49ba0d381fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-1-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259702968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259702967"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" cce51a89-ef88-460c-b44c-a49ba0d381fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-1-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259713750","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259713749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259714052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259714052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259714655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259714655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259717620","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259717620"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwangalie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGALIE"," userResponse":" MWANGALIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259720430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259720430"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259721064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259721064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259721806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259721806"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259724807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259724807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIAMKA"," userResponse":" AKIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259726371","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259726370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAZIPANGA"," userResponse":" ANAZIPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259726953","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259726953"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259727617","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259727617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259728461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259728461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259729363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259729363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259729480","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259729480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259729992","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259729992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEZA"," userResponse":" MEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259732671","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259732671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259733594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259733594"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259733996","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259733996"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259734100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259734100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259735223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259735223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259735456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259735456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259735959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259735959"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259736204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259736204"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259737067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259737067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259737549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259737549"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259740393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259740393"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259741285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259741285"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259741767","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259741767"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259741869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259741869"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259742881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259742881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259743136","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259743136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259743800","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259743800"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" WENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259744632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259744632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZINI"," userResponse":" KAZINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259747658","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259747658"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BALI"," userResponse":" BALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259747950","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259747950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259748682","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259748682"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259748965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259748965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259749048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259749048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259750121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259750121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259750363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259750363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259750986","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259750986"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259752028","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259752028"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIO"," userResponse":" WALIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259752191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259752191"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259752944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259752944"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADENI"," userResponse":" MADENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259753427","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259753427"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259756532","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259756531"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259757075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259757075"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259757137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259757137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259757999","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259757999"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259758401","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259758401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259758484","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259758484"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259759467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259759467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259759659","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259759659"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259760353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259760353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259760857","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259760857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259761040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259761039"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259761813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259761813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DHATI"," userResponse":" DHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259764818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259764818"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259764910","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259764910"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259765923","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259765923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" KIZAMBARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259767535","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259767535"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITUMIA"," userResponse":" ANAITUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259768838","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259768837"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259769281","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259769281"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259769723","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259769723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259770876","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259770875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOHITAJI"," userResponse":" WANAOHITAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259771548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259771548"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259772115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259772115"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259774723","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259774723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259775406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259775406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259776508","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259776508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUPENDA"," userResponse":" HUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259777181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259777181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259778543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259778543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHI"," userResponse":" KUFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259781205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259781205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPENDI"," userResponse":" HAPENDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259781997","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259781997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGOMVI"," userResponse":" UGOMVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259782740","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259782740"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259783232","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259783232"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITA"," userResponse":" VITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259786525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259786525"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWAALIKA"," userResponse":" HUWAALIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259787527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259787527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259788599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259788599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGALIA"," userResponse":" KUANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259789363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259789363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" RUNINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259790025","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259790025"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259790428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259790428"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKA"," userResponse":" DUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259790961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259790961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259794482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259794482"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWATEMBELEA"," userResponse":" HUWATEMBELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259795494","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259795494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAGONJWA"," userResponse":" WAGONJWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259796027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259796027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259796750","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259796749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZEE"," userResponse":" WAZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259797613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259797613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259798067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259798067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259798599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259798599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259801573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259801573"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259802845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259802845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" APITAPO"," userResponse":" APITAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259803788","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259803788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259804511","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259804511"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259804834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259804834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259805427","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259805427"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259806407","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259806407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259808574","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259808574"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259809467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259809467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259812211","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259812211"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259813304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259813304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" HUFURAHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259813502","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259813501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259814177","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259814177"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259815757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259815756"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259816603","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259816603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259816791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259816791"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259817295","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259817295"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259817872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259817872"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259818306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259818306"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259818775","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259818774"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259819537","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259819537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259820898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259820898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIANGALIENI"," userResponse":" ZIANGALIENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259823262","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259823261"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259823425","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259823425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259823580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259823580"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259824199","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259824198"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259824653","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259824653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259825169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259825168"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259825647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259825646"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259826172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259826172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259828974","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259828973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259829038","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259829037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 30afb546-410f-4080-af5e-e13b1b4bd225"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259838085","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259838085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" e6ff5ea9-c85a-4af5-a9c4-9e9b731382cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-u-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259841906","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259841906"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" e6ff5ea9-c85a-4af5-a9c4-9e9b731382cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_o-i-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259847328","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259847328"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" e6ff5ea9-c85a-4af5-a9c4-9e9b731382cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_o-i-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259850834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259850834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" e6ff5ea9-c85a-4af5-a9c4-9e9b731382cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_u-i-e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259855274","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259855274"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" e6ff5ea9-c85a-4af5-a9c4-9e9b731382cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-i-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259859241","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259859241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" e6ff5ea9-c85a-4af5-a9c4-9e9b731382cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-o-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259864978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259864978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" e6ff5ea9-c85a-4af5-a9c4-9e9b731382cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-o-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259876299","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259876299"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" f0c655b3-9812-47c5-a8ad-9a066b3512fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-9-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259883102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259883102"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" f0c655b3-9812-47c5-a8ad-9a066b3512fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-5-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259888655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259888655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" f0c655b3-9812-47c5-a8ad-9a066b3512fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_1-8-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259893409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259893409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" f0c655b3-9812-47c5-a8ad-9a066b3512fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-7-8"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259900222","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259900222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" f0c655b3-9812-47c5-a8ad-9a066b3512fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-5-9"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259907899","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259907899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" f0c655b3-9812-47c5-a8ad-9a066b3512fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_5-0-8"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259913623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259913623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" f0c655b3-9812-47c5-a8ad-9a066b3512fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_5-1-2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259919303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259919303"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" f0c655b3-9812-47c5-a8ad-9a066b3512fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_3-5-0"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259924908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259924908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" f0c655b3-9812-47c5-a8ad-9a066b3512fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_9-1-3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259930178","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259930178"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" f0c655b3-9812-47c5-a8ad-9a066b3512fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-4-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259936641","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259936641"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" f0c655b3-9812-47c5-a8ad-9a066b3512fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-4-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259947545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259947544"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259951193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259951193"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" asali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259952774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259952774"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259956767","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259956766"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anaoga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259958335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259958335"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259963778","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259963777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259965376","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259965375"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259969446","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259969445"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259971060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259971060"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alicheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259974939","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259974939"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alicheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259976536","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259976536"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andika"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259980200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259980199"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andika"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259981787","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259981787"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anasoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259986075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259986075"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anasoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259987715","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259987714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akalala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259992602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259992601"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" akalala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259994170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259994170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259997879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259997878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259999481","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259999481"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anacheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260003793","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260003792"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anacheza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260005378","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260005378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260008662","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260008662"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.40__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260010672","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260010671"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260010832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260010832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260120361","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260120360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" a145205d-029d-4386-acf0-19a410791cfa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.40__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" anguka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260120461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260120461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" ca6b94b1-0402-4d27-a626-e487ce5f4652"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260130706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260130706"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" b52e14d9-68b0-4018-b4c6-82882cb7e7fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_u-o-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260133982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260133982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" b52e14d9-68b0-4018-b4c6-82882cb7e7fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-o-i"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260137709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260137709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" b52e14d9-68b0-4018-b4c6-82882cb7e7fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_o-a-u"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260141009","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260141009"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" b52e14d9-68b0-4018-b4c6-82882cb7e7fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_i-a-o"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260144370","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260144369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" b52e14d9-68b0-4018-b4c6-82882cb7e7fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_i-e-a"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260147377","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260147377"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" b52e14d9-68b0-4018-b4c6-82882cb7e7fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-e-i"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260150730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260150729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" b52e14d9-68b0-4018-b4c6-82882cb7e7fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_u-e-a"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260154417","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260154416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" b52e14d9-68b0-4018-b4c6-82882cb7e7fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_i-o-a"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260157896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260157896"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" b52e14d9-68b0-4018-b4c6-82882cb7e7fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-o-a"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260161325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260161325"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" b52e14d9-68b0-4018-b4c6-82882cb7e7fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-o-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260167067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260167060"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" b52e14d9-68b0-4018-b4c6-82882cb7e7fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-o-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260177823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260177823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 536b69b3-3511-4a86-9a8a-1c8476436205"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-6-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260182244","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260182244"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 536b69b3-3511-4a86-9a8a-1c8476436205"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_5-8-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260186667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260186666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 536b69b3-3511-4a86-9a8a-1c8476436205"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-3-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260196993","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260196993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 536b69b3-3511-4a86-9a8a-1c8476436205"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_6-0-3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260203986","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260203986"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 536b69b3-3511-4a86-9a8a-1c8476436205"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-9-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260208760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260208760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 536b69b3-3511-4a86-9a8a-1c8476436205"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_9-4-1"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260213560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260213560"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 536b69b3-3511-4a86-9a8a-1c8476436205"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3-5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260222156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260222156"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 536b69b3-3511-4a86-9a8a-1c8476436205"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-8-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260228850","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260228850"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 536b69b3-3511-4a86-9a8a-1c8476436205"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_7-4-1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260234377","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260234377"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 536b69b3-3511-4a86-9a8a-1c8476436205"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_7-4-1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260240479","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260240478"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 536b69b3-3511-4a86-9a8a-1c8476436205"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260246066","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260246066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 536b69b3-3511-4a86-9a8a-1c8476436205"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260252560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260252559"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 536b69b3-3511-4a86-9a8a-1c8476436205"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260277300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260277300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 7db22b1e-816d-42e9-b52d-7501db909120"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_u_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260283996","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260283996"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 7db22b1e-816d-42e9-b52d-7501db909120"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_a_e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260291545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260291544"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 7db22b1e-816d-42e9-b52d-7501db909120"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_a_e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260298242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260298242"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 7db22b1e-816d-42e9-b52d-7501db909120"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_i_e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260304884","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260304884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 7db22b1e-816d-42e9-b52d-7501db909120"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_u_a"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260311501","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260311501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 7db22b1e-816d-42e9-b52d-7501db909120"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_a_i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260318112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260318112"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 7db22b1e-816d-42e9-b52d-7501db909120"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_e_o"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260324795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260324794"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 7db22b1e-816d-42e9-b52d-7501db909120"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_i_e"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260331471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260331471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 7db22b1e-816d-42e9-b52d-7501db909120"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_a_e"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260338076","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260338076"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 7db22b1e-816d-42e9-b52d-7501db909120"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_a_u"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260344745","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260344745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 7db22b1e-816d-42e9-b52d-7501db909120"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_a_i_o"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.lc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260353727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260353726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_190707"," gameId":" 7db22b1e-816d-42e9-b52d-7501db909120"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.lc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_a_i_o"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}